[music begins]
♪ Take this pink ribbon
Off my eyes ♪
♪ I'm exposed
And it's no big surprise ♪
♪ Don't you think I know
Exactly where I stand ♪
♪ This world is forcing me
To hold your hand ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm just a girl
Little ol' me ♪
♪ Well, don't let me
Out of your sight ♪
♪ Oh, I'm just a girl
All pretty and petite ♪
♪ So don't let me
Have any rights ♪
♪ Oh
I've had it up to here ♪
♪ The moment
That I step outside ♪
♪ So many reasons
For me to run and hide ♪
♪ I can't do the little things
I hold so dear ♪
♪ It's all
Those little things ♪
♪ That I fear ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm just a girl
I'd rather not be ♪
♪ 'Cause they won't
Let me drive late at night ♪
♪ Oh, I'm just a girl
Guess I'm some kind of frea♪
♪ 'Cause they all sit and stare
With their eyes ♪
♪ Oh, I'm just a girl ♪
♪ Take a good look at me ♪
♪ Just your typical prototype ♪
♪ Oh, I've had it up to here ♪
♪ Oh
Am I making myself clear? ♪
♪ I'm just a girl ♪
♪ I'm just a girl in the world ♪
♪ That's all
That you'll let me be! ♪
♪ Oh, I'm just girl
Living in captivity ♪
♪ Your rule of thumb
Makes me worrisome ♪
♪ Oh, I'm just a girl
What's my destiny? ♪
♪ What I've succumbed to
Is making me numb ♪
♪ Oh, I'm just a girl
My apologies ♪
♪ What I've become
Is so burdensome ♪
♪ Oh, I'm just a girl
Lucky me ♪
♪ Tweedledum
There's no comparison ♪
♪ Oh, I've had it up to ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ I've had it up to here ♪